I've decided that if he loses, I'll destroy half the city.
こいつが負けたら
街を半分ぶっ壊すことにした
Doesn't that make things more exciting?
そのほうがワクワクすんだろ？
gokigen yo doukashitan darou?
How are you? Is something wrong?
ごきげんよう どうかしたんだろ？
kao wo mireba isshun de wakaru yo
I can tell just by looking at you.
顔を見れば一瞬でわかるよ
senrigan senrigan? messou nai desu
Am I psychic? Of course not.
千里眼千里眼？
めっそうないです
taikutsu GIRL megumaretai no kai
Bored girl, do you want to find happiness?
退屈ガール 恵まれたいのかい
hantei wa shingi no renzoku de
Let's think it through and decide.
判定は審議の連続で
VENUS SUSTAIN
Venus Sustain.
ヴィーナスサステイン
odoru machinami
The city dances.
踊る街並み
PERFECTLY EUPHORIA
Perfectly, Euphoria!
Perfectly Euphoria！
nandemo nai youna kotoba de naitari suru shi
I end up crying over the smallest things.
何でもないような
言葉で泣いたりするし
hora bokutachi nante
Come on, our
ほら 僕達なんて
zentei no nai
temporary passion
juubun tekido ni
lives are
十分適度に
zentei no nai
a temporary passion
DRAMATIC sa
reasonably dramatic.
ドラマチックさ
saikou no wa
the best passion
karuku SUPER STAR
We're almost like super stars!
軽くスーパースター
ORION wo nazoru konna fukai yoru
Looking up at Orion late at night.
オリオンをなぞる こんな深い夜
tsunagaretai hanasaretai
I want to connect. I want to be free.
つながりたい 離されたい
tsumari hanshinhangi acchi kocchi
Basically, I'm not sure and can't decide.
つまり半信半疑あっちこっち
shin mirai wo negau kuuzenzetsugo no
I pray for a new future. The greatest one yet.
新未来を願う
空前絶後の
kotoba ga moshi, moshi tsumugeru nara jikan ga tomaru yo
If I could spin words, time would stop.
言葉がもし もし紡げるなら
時間が止まるよ
koko de owaru hazu ga nai no ni
"There's no way it can end here."
「ココデオワルハズガナイノニ」
タイガーさん…
Mr. Tiger...
Thank you all for waiting!
さあ！　お待たせいたしました
この男の登場です
A new competitor has entered the stadium.
The fourth of Seven Matches, Mister Jake's next challenger...
セブンマッチ 第４戦
ジェイク様がお相手するのは
復讐に燃える復讐君
The Revenge Boy who is out for vengeance!
There she goes again with those damn nicknames!
また変なあだ名つけやがって
ええ？
おやおや？　どういうことでしょう？
Oh? What's going on? I don't see Mister Jake.
ジェイク様の姿が見えませんね
ふっ へへへへへ
にははははは
いやぁはっは〜！
はっ
やは〜は〜！
ああっと！
ジェイク様の美しき奇襲攻撃！
Wow! Mister Jake stages a beautiful ambush!
ぐおっ！
ぐっ
ふん！
ひっひ〜
であ！
がっ
くっ
うわあ　しょっぱい蹴り
Wow, that was some lousy kick.
くっ…
There's something I want to ask you.
お前に聞きたいことがある
復讐君の攻撃も ジェイク様の前では
まったく歯がたちません
Not even Revenge Boy's attack
stands a chance against Mister Jake!
あっ
Answer me!
答えろ！
なぜ父さんと母さんを殺した！
Why did you kill my parents?!
何の恨みがあって２人を！
What did you have against them?!
ぐあっ
Let's forget about the past and enjoy the now.
昔のことなんか忘れたよ
今を楽しもうぜ
ふふふ…
What speed.
なんてスピードだ
攻撃をすべて見切るとは…
He's reading all of his attacks.
もう 何で能力使わないのよ
Why isn't he using his power?
同じ能力のタイガーがやられたんだから
Tiger has the same power as Barnaby, and he was defeated.
That's why Barnaby can't use his recklessly.
うかつに使えないんでしょう
でも このままじゃこの街
But at this rate, the city is going to be destroyed.
ん？
あっ
ボンジュール ヒーロー
Bonjour, Heroes.
電波ジャックの準備が整ったわ
We've set up the signal jack.
Quite frankly, Barnaby could lose at any time.
正直 バーナビーはいつ負けても
おかしくない
I want you three uninjured Heroes to remove
柱が壊される前に
無傷の３人はパワードスーツから
マッドベアを回収すること
the Mad Bears from the powered exosuits before
before they destroy the support columns.
あ…
それでいいのよね？
That should do it, right?
折紙
Origami?
はい　動きを止められるはずです
Yes. This should stop them.
Blue Rose, you take North Bronze.
ブルーローズはノースブロンズ
Dragon Kid, you take South.
ドラゴンキッドはサウス
Fire Emblem, you take—
ファイヤーエンブレムは
俺も行く
I'm going too.
あっ
なっ
Where should I go?
俺は…
どこに向かえばいい？
Wait... Are you crazy?!
ちょ…　何言ってるんですか？
ワイルド君 そんな状態で…
Mister Wild, you're in no condition to—
I can't...
こんなとこで
寝てられっかよ
just lie down.
おい アニエス！
俺はどこに向かえば…
Hey, Agnes! Where should I go?
いい加減にしてよ！
Cut it out!
えっ
今のあんたに来られたって 超迷惑！
Even if you come with us, you'll be nothing but trouble!
超役立たず！　超足手まとい！
You'll be totally useless! And totally getting in our way!
ああん？
What?!
はあ　ちょっと
Guys... Now is not the time to be fighting.
今は喧嘩してる場合じゃないんだけど
あんたはバーナビーの
パートナーなんでしょ？
You're Barnaby's partner, aren't you?
だったら ジェイク倒す方法でも
考えてあげて！
Then you should be thinking of a way to help him defeat Jake!
あ！
もう…
Jeez...
ふん
Damn!
だっ！
ブルーローズの言うとおりだ
Blue Rose is right. Stay put for now.
今は大人しくしとけ
Revenge Boy looks like he's struggling,
苦しそうな復讐君と対象的に
but Mister Jake hasn't broken a sweat.
息一つ乱れないジェイク様
Bravo!
あっぱれですわ
なあ 俺が寝てる間
バニーの攻撃は当たったのか？
Say, while I was sleeping,
did any of Bunny's attacks make contact?
いや すべてバリアで
シャットアウトされている
No.
They were all shut out by that force field.
まだ 誰もジェイクに一撃すら…
No one has hit Jake even once, yet.
But yours did, right, Kotetsu?
でも虎徹のは当たったよな？
ん？
Huh?
ほら　お前が倒れたとき
You know, when you collapsed.
あんなの攻撃じゃねえよ
That doesn't count as an attack.
うわあああ！
ぐはははは
くっ
If I keep attacking him,
攻撃を繰り出していれば
必ず隙が生まれるはず
I am bound to break through at some point.
隙さえ作ることができれば
If I can just get him to let his guard down...
It's a waste of time trying to think about it.
考えるだけ 無駄無駄
まあそんなに隙が欲しいなら
But if you really want me to let my guard down that badly...
であ！
ぐっ
Oh dear, both of them are hidden in the mist.
あらら　２人の姿が
もやに隠れてしまいましたわ
Where could they be?
どこにいるのかしら？
ぐう
はい 注目
Pay close attention. I'm wide open right now.
今の俺 隙しかねえぞ？
All right...
ようし！
ぐあっ
なっ！
You'll never defeat me.
お前には一生 倒せねえよ
After all, I can hear your thoughts loud and clear.
なんたって こっちには
お前の心が丸聞こえなんだからな
くっ…
どした？
もう おねむの時間か？
What's wrong? Is it time for bed already?
ええ？
Well?
Is this your idea of justice, Heroes?
お前たちの掲げる正義とは
この程度か？
This is bad.
やべえよこれ
どうなっちまうんだ
What's going to happen to us?!
Let's show them some girl-power!
女子の底力
見せてやりましょう
女子？　若干違う方がいる気が？
"Girl"? One of us doesn't quite fit that description.
ごめん　僕がボーイッシュだから…
Sorry, is it because I'm a tomboy?
いや…　じゃなくて
I'm not talking about you.
What? Are you saying that I'm not one of the girls?
何？　あたしが女子じゃないってこと？
Ugh! These two are too much for me!
もう！　めんどくさい この２人！
３人とも 準備はいい？
Are you all ready? Barnaby is still on the losing end.
相変わらずバーナビーは劣勢よ
こうなったらあなたたちで
この街を救うのよ
It's now up to you three to save this city!
はい！
Yes, ma'am.
おいしい玉露と
A delicious green tea...
And a gorgeous boyfriend.
素敵な恋人
What a wonderful life.
幸せですわ
ジャミングシステム スタンバイ
Prepare to jam the systems!
Activating in five...
作動まであと５秒
４秒
four...
three...
two...
one...
作戦開始
Begin the operation!
んふ
は〜い　マッドベアちゃん
脱ぎ脱ぎちまちょうね
Okay, you cute little Mad Bears. It's time to undress!
どあっ
何の音？
What's that sound?
あっ 何か光ってるよ！
Something's glowing!
Activating self-defense program.
自己防衛プログラムが作動します
うっそ…
You're kidding me!
ぐっ
Whoa, time out!
ちょ たんまたんま
ぐう！
くっ むごい
This is brutal...
う〜ん ああ　ぶっちゃけがっかりだな
What a disappointment.
こいつが２位なんて しょぼすぎ
I can't believe this loser is ranked second amongst Heroes.
ぐっ
ただいま 復讐君がジェイク様との
格の違いに絶望している様子を
We are now seeing Revenge Boy
lost in despair as he realizes the difference in power
ご覧いただいております
between him and Mister Jake.
If I could only get through his force field...
バリアさえ破れれば…
Oh, too bad.
あ〜 残念
ぐあっ
You'll never beat me at this rate.
それじゃ 俺は死んでも倒せねえぜ？
You don't even know half of what makes me so great.
お前は俺様の偉大さを
半分も理解できてねえよ
能力が１つだって言ったか？
Did I ever say that I had only one power?
俺？
What?!
何！
俺は…
You see...
俺は神から許されたんだ
God has allowed me...
to have two powers!
能力を２つ持つことをな！
あっははははは
Two powers?!
能力が２つだと？
I've never heard of such a thing!
そんなやつ 聞いたことねえぞ
おっと これ以上ヒントはなしだ
Oops, that's all the clues I can give you.
さあ！　もっと遊ぼうぜ？
Come on, let's play some more.
What clues?! He's making fun of us!
何がヒントだ！　なめやがって！
でも これで１つ はっきりした
One thing is clear.
Huh?
あ？
俺たちの攻撃が 当たらなかったのは
His other power is the reason why our attacks couldn't hit him.
もう１個の能力のせいだ
つまり ジェイクが能力を使って
攻撃を見極めていると言うのか？
Are you saying that Jake used his power to read our attacks?
いったい どんな力なんでしょう？
What could his other power be?
あっ！
俺には すべて聞こえてんだ
I can hear everything.
So that's it!
そうか
能力が わかったのか？
You figured out his power?
ああ すぐバニーに伝えないと
Yeah. I've got to tell Bunny right away.
タイガーさん！
Mr. Tiger!
はあ はあ…
お前の体はボロボロだ
You are a wreck.
他のやつに任せて…
Somebody else should go.
It has to be me.
俺じゃなきゃダメなんだ
俺じゃなきゃ伝えられねんだよ
I have to be the one to tell him.
But you're...
だけど お前
うおおおおお！
How can I defeat this guy?
どうすれば こいつを倒せる？
もう１つの能力って何なんだ？
What's his other power?
ひひひ
うおおおおあ！
あっ
It can't be!
まさか…
ハンドレッドパワーで治癒力を高め
You used your Hundred Power to speed up your healing?!
傷を癒したのか？
ああ 完全回復だ
Yup, a complete recovery!
もう心配はいらねえ
I'm fine now.
安心してくれ
So don't worry.
んじゃ さくっと行ってくるわ
Well, I'll be off.
I didn't know he could heal like that...
あそこまで治っちゃうんだ
やせ我慢しやがって
That idiot. Acting like it's nothing...
え？
Huh?
あっ
ぐう…
んふ
あっ
タイガー！！　何してるんだ
Hey, Mr. Saito. I have a favor to ask.
なあ 斉藤さん
あんたに頼みがある
ぐあっ
Uh-oh! Revenge Boy is down for a record thirtieth time!
ああっと 復讐君！
記念すべき30回目のダウン！
I can't take any more hits like this...
これ以上攻撃されたらもう…
でも 今能力を発動させても勝算は…
But even if I activate my powers, I don't know if I can win.
さっさと能力だしてみろよ？
Hurry up and use your power already.
早くしねえと死んじまうぞ？
You'll end up dead if you don't.
Oh, I get it.
ああ そっか
パパとママに会いたいのか
You're dying to see your daddy and mommy, aren't you?
ぐっ
あ？
じゃ親子そろって殺してやる
In that case, I will send you to join them!
よっ
ぐあ！
このまま終わって
I can't let it end here!
たまるかあああああ！
Wow, there it is!
ああ きたきた！
ぐっ
くっ
はいいい！
くあっ
くっ
もう！　何やってんの みんな！
What's taking you so long?! We're running out of time!
時間がないのよ！
We know that! We're doing the best we can, woman!
んなことは分かってんだよ！
必死にやってんだろ！
These guys are pretty tough!
やっぱり こいつら結構強いよ！
There're too many of them to take on with just the three of us!
こんないっぱい ３人じゃ無理！
この作戦…
Has our plan... failed?
失敗なの？
もうバーナビーも限界です
Barnaby's at his limit.
能力を発動しても やられっぱなしで…
He's getting beaten up even while using his power.
If he loses, they're going to destroy half of the city.
このまま負けたら街が半分…
No, they probably won't stop there.
いや 半分では済まんだろうな
戦いが終われば
Once this battle is over,
我々がパワードスーツに
反撃したことに気づくはず
they'll realize that we attacked their powered exosuits.
They might destroy all of the support columns in their anger.
怒りに任せて
柱を全て爆破させるかもしれん
They can't!
そんな！
もはやバーナビーに託すしかない
It's all up to Barnaby now.
どした どした？　こんなもんか？
What's wrong? Is that all you've got?
I can't touch him even while using my Hundred Power.
ハンドレッドパワーでも
触れることすらできないなんて
チェスト！　たたた〜！
Bang! Bang-bang-bang!
ぐあっ
Whoopsie daisy. I hit him a little too far away.
あ〜らら
飛ばしすぎちまった
ふっ ふははは
がっ　ぐっ
ぐあっ　くっ
Am I going to lose?
このまま僕は負けてしまうのか？
Even though I've lived for this day?
この日のためだけに生きてきたのに
父さん…　母さん…
Father... Mother...
く…
え？
だいじょぶか？　バニー？
Are you all right, Bunny?
なっ
おじさん！
Old Man! Why are you here?
何しにきたんですか！
ぐっ
だいいち あなた体…
What about your injury?
ああ
あんぐらい へっちゃらへっちゃら
Oh that? It was nothing.
お〜い！
Hey! Come down already!
ん？
さっさと降りてこいよ！
Wait a second!
あ ちょっと待てよ
また僕の邪魔をするつもりですか？
Are you trying to get in my way again?
もう時間がないんです
I don't have time for this.
ジェイクの能力が分かったんだ
I figured out Jake's other power.
ええ？
攻撃が当たらないのは
俺たちの動きを読んでいるから
We're unable to hit him because he can read our movements.
え？
つまり あいつの２つ目の能力は
In other words...
His second power...
耳がいいってことだ
is good hearing!
は？
Huh?
During my battle, Jake said that he could hear everything.
俺との戦闘で ジェイクは
すべて聞こえてるって言った
それが答えだったんだ
That's the answer!
やつの能力は
His power is...
超聴覚
super hearing.
筋肉の動く音を聞いて
次の動きを察知していたんだ
He was listening to the sound of our muscles moving
to predict our next move.
いや
No way...
ん？
Use this to defeat him!
斉藤さん特製の超音波弾だ
It's Mr. Saito's special ultrasonic grenade.
ジェイクの耳を潰し
その隙に攻撃しろ
Attack Jake after you destroyed his ears with this.
僕はあなたを信じられない
I can't trust you.
あなたは僕を信じてくれなかった
You didn't trust me. That's why...
だからもう…
バニー！
Bunny!
ぐっ
My power's going to run out soon.
もうすぐ能力は切れる
最後は 自分だけを信じて攻撃します
I'll only trust in myself and make my final attack.
ん？
血？
Blood?
Your body...
あなた体！
Are you ready yet?!
まだかよ！
ぐあっ
へっへへ
ぐっ
やっと戻ってきたか
So you finally came back.
Please trust me.
俺を信じてくれ
Get ready, Jake.
ジェイク 覚悟しろ！
Too bad. I heard your plan.
はい 残念
お前の作戦聞こえちゃってんぞ
ていうか何だ？　俺の能力
But come on, you think my power is super hearing?
超聴覚って…
大はずれじゃねえか
You are way off.
であ！　くっ
ふんっ
ふんっはあ！　ひへへへ
Take this!
くらええ！
へへ〜ん
あっ
ば〜ん
Bang.
ぐっ
あんなもんで
俺を倒せるわけねえだろ！
You really think you could beat me with that?
へっ
ぐ あ ああ
Now, Barnaby!
今だ！　バーナビー！
でやああ！
ぐう！
でい！
Mister Jake!
ジェイク様！
うああ… ああ…
肋骨折れた…
He broke my rib.
くっ
あああっ
であ！
ふぐっ
い…　痛えよう
It hurts... It hurts. Help me.
痛え 助けて
殺さないで　ヒーローなんだろ？
Don't kill me. You're a Hero, right?
頼むよ…
Please...
ぐうう！
ぬううう！
くうっ
はあっ はあっ…
Spend the rest of your life repenting for your sins.
一生かけて 罪を償え
やった…　やった！
He did it... He did it!
やったー！
はあ
You don't need to thank me.
礼はいいぞ？
お礼なんて言いませんよ
I wasn't going to.
あ？
Huh?
なんで僕を だましたんです？
Why did you trick me?
最初から閃光弾って
言えばいいじゃないですか
You should have said
it was a flash grenade from the beginning.
He'd figure it out if I did that!
んなことしたらバレちまうだろ
あいつ心が読める能力なんだぞ？
He has the ability to read minds.
心が読める？
Read minds?
I thought you said he had super hearing?
耳がいいんじゃ…
You didn't figure it out yet?
ま〜だ 気づいてなかったか
は？
Huh?
You sure are slow.
鈍いなぁ
どうやって わかったんです？
How did you figure it out?
いやさ
Well... He referred to me as "Kotetsu."
あいつ 俺のこと虎徹って呼んだんだ
ん？
Damn you, Kotetsu!
おらあ！　くそ虎徹！
I haven't revealed my real name to the public.
俺の本名は公になってない
So how did he know my name?
なのになぜ
俺の名前を知っていたのか
Calm down, Kaburagi Kotetsu.
落ち着け鏑木虎徹
必ず突破口があるはずだ
There should be a way to attack him.
あんときの心の声を
聞いたんじゃねえかってな
That's when I figured
he must have been listening to my thoughts.
だから全部聞こえてる…
That's why he said he could hear everything.
そう
Exactly!
にしても 超聴覚って何ですか？
But super hearing?
筋肉の音を聞く？
Listening to the sound of our muscles?
もう少し真実味のあることを
言ってくださいよ
Couldn't you have tried to think of something more believable?
僕があなたの言うことを信じなかったら
どうするつもりだったんですか？
What if I hadn't believed you?
そりゃないだろ
I knew that wouldn't happen.
え？
Huh?
だって俺は…
Because...
I believed that you would trust me.
お前が俺を信じてくれるって
信じてたからな
なっ
く…
ふっ
にひ
Hand over Mister Jake!
ジェイク様を渡しなさい
What?
何？
Did you forget that we have hostages?
人質がいるのをお忘れ？
市民の命が
どうなっても いいのかしら？
Don't you care what happens to the people of this city?
貴様ら！
You bastard...
ふ へへへへ
How unfortunate for you!
残念だったな　へへっ
You're the one who's unfortunate.
残念なのはお前だよ
Huh?
あ？
Where are your hostages?
人質なんてどこにいんだよ？
Hi!
は〜い
We're here live
こちらは今 パワードスーツを
破壊したところで〜す
where all the powered exosuits have just been destroyed!
うう！
This stuffed animal is so cute!
このぬいぐるみ かわいいわ〜
ちゅっちゅ
Smooch, smooch!
And now back to...
スタジオさ〜ん
お返ししま〜す
...the studio!
くっ
You can't get away with this anymore.
もうお前らの好きにはさせねえぞ
Hey, Kriem!
おおい クリーム！　受け止めろ！
Catch me!
ジェイク様〜！
Mister Jake!
うおおおおおおお！
Oh no, you don't!
させるか！
うあああああ！
どあ！　くっ！　ぐあっ
Ow ow ow...
あ痛たた
Don't get in my way!
邪魔すんな！
うあ！
きゃあああああ！
はあああ？
バーナビー！　バーナビー！
Barnaby, Barnaby, Barnaby!
バーナビー！　バーナビー…
Yes!
イエス！
Master...
坊っちゃん
They did it.
やりましたね！
ヒーローＴＶ史上
最高のショーになったわ
This is the best episode of HERO TV ever!
Uh... right.
はい…
Barnaby has met his destiny
宿命を背負ったバーナビーが
ついに両親の仇をとり
to finally avenge his parents and save your lives.
あなたがたの命を守ったのです
バーナビーに ヒーローたちに拍手を
Please give Barnaby and the other Heroes a round of applause!
Evil is destined to be annihilated.
やはり悪は滅びる さだめだ
And we must not forget our other hero.
そして もう１人の英雄を
忘れてはなりません
The man who oversaw this entire operation
今回のウロボロス撲滅作戦
すべての指揮をお取りになった
to destroy Ouroboros.
Give a big round of applause to our mayor.
市長にも盛大な拍手を
あっ
You two are a complete wreck.
あんたたちボロボロね
You guys look terrible.
顔色悪いよ？
I told you to get some rest!
もう…　寝てろって言ったのに
あっ
You were truly magnificent out there, Barnaby! Truly!
バーナビー君　いやあ
とてもクールだったよ！　とても！
ああ 助かったぜ　恩にきる
Yeah, you saved us all. Thanks!
最高です！　バーナビーさん
You're the best, Mr. Barnaby!
We really are grateful, Handsome!
ホントにありがとね　ハンサム
ちっ
Why the dissatisfied look on your face?
何もの欲しそうな顔してるんですか？
ん？
You want to get some praise too, don't you?
自分も褒めて ほしいんでしょ？
That's not it!
そんなんじゃねえよ！
Fine, whatever. Let's ignore these two idiots
はいはい　おばかコンビはほっといて
お見舞い行きましょ
and go visit everyone in the hospital, shall we?
は〜い
Okay!
えっ バカってなんですか？
Who are you calling an idiot? Don't group me with him!
この人と一緒にしないでくださいよ
くっ
うう あ痛っ
Ow!
Why are you just standing there?
何ぼけっとしてるんですか？
Oh, it's nothing.
いや ちょっとな
Come on. Let's go, Kotetsu.
もうさっさと行きますよ
虎徹さん
Right.
おう
ん？　お前今…
Hey, did you just call me...
ふっ
ちょっと待てよ　バニー
Hey, wait, Bunny!
Wait up!
待てって！
My wounds hurt!
俺 傷痛いんですけど〜？
僕が消え 遠い未来で
boku ga kie tooi mirai de kaseki ni nattara
When I die and become a fossil in the far future,
化石になったら
人は僕に何を見るだろう
hito wa boku ni nani wo miru darou?
what will people see me as?
分析して 名を付けて
bunseki shite na wo tsukete kaidoku wo shitemo
They may try to analyze, name, and understand me,
解読をしても
愛した人は僕しか知らない
aishita hito wa boku shika shiranai
but only I will know the person I loved.
ハロー　生きること
HELLO ikiru koto
Hello, existence.
君の他に 君はできない
kimi no hoka ni kimi wa dekinai
Only you alone can live your life.
輝き続ける光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
僕らは何を感じられるだろう
bokura wa nani wo kanjirareru darou?
What can we feel from it?
奇跡は宇宙だけじゃないよ
kiseki wa uchuu dake janai yo
The universe isn't the only miracle.
輝き続ける光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
目を閉じたって 閉じきれないよ
me wo tojitatte tojikirenaiyo
You can try to shut your eyes, but you can't shut out your heart.
あの星さえ 持てなかった心
ano hoshi sae motenakatta kokoro
It's something that even the stars did not possess.
ども！　TIGER ＆ BUNNYの
いつも深爪ぎみなほう
虎徹です
Hi! I'm Kotetsu, the member of "Tiger & Bunny"
いやあ ようやく一安心
who always ends up clipping his nails too short!
Things are finally settled. We've come a long way.
ここまできたか
っていうか
これからどうなっちゃうんだ？
次回　TIGER ＆ BUNNY
That aside, what's going to happen now?
Love is blind
Next time on TIGER & BUNNY:
あはっ ラブって…
L-Love?